{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"338/42",
			"answer":"338/42",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"169/14",
			"answer":"169/14",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"494/38",
			"answer":"494/38",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"609/76",
			"answer":"609/76",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"910/65",
			"answer":"910/65",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"88/43",
			"answer":"88/43",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"490/98",
			"answer":"490/98",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"872/67",
			"answer":"872/67",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"496/62",
			"answer":"496/62",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"979/97",
			"answer":"979/97",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}